

Samuel Morgan-Tyghe

Web Developer



Professional Summary

Solution-driven Web Developer, adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using Various tech stacks, Typescript-Chakra, Jamstack (Hugo-Contentful) and React-Redux. Built products for desktop and mobile app users over 2 + years, meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs (Django, Node, .Net), third-party integrations and databases.

Proficient Fine Artist knowledgeable about
Graphic design Trends, Experienced in
Photoshop, Figma and website design. Side
projects include working on Automated designs
and artwork.



Work History

2021-10 -Current

Web Developer, Front End Developer

HHL, Newcastle, NET

- Developing websites and apps
- Upholding high standards of coding
- Fixing security vulnerabilities
- Main point of contact between an international team
- running tests on SEO and Accessibility

2021-06 -2021-09

React Developer

In-House





Address

Leith, EH64AG, Edinburgh

Phone

07376080332

E-mail

samuelmorganvisual@gmail. com



React (Functional + Class)
CSS (Modules, Bootstrap,

Tailwind)

JS-IN-CSS (ChakraUI, MaterialUI, Styled Components)

Webpack, Gulp

Redux (Connect, Toolkit)

TypeScript

SEO, Security, Accessibility

Jamstack (Hugo, Gatsby) + Contentful

SQL, GraphQL



React

 Working to bridge the gap between Graphic Design and Front end developer Teams Bug fixing

HTML

CSS

Typescript

• Update Styling

• Optimise Components



Education

2012-01 -2015-01 Bachelor's degree: Digital Arts

Bath Spa University



Projects

- hedgehog lab
 - https://cmspi.com/ (Internal)
 Typescript, Node, React-query, Tanstack,
 Chart.js, React-Select.
 - https://cotytrip.com/ (Internal)
 React functional + class components, Redux + toolkit + Persist, Typescript, PWA, Html2Canvas, MarkerJs2, React-Select,
 - https://halosystem.halosolutions.com/login (Internal)
 SPA, Scaling up (Pagination of data, Optimising performance),
 - https://www.securityforum.org/solutionsand-insights/standard-of-good-practicefor-information- security-2020/ React Context, husky (lint & test git hooks), SPA,
 - https://admin.lugmety.com/login (Internal)
 GraphQL, React Awesome Query Builder
 - https://howbusyistoon.com/
 Gatsby, CSS Modules, Atom methodology, contentful.

In-House

- https://in-house.com/
 Next.js, Jira, Scrum, Storybook, Styled
 Components.